<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Unity on Stork&#39;Studios</title>
    <link>https://storkstudios.github.io/tags/unity/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Unity on Stork&#39;Studios</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 23:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://storkstudios.github.io/tags/unity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Demo 2.2 Patchnotes</title>
      <link>https://storkstudios.github.io/blog/demo_2_2_patchnotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 23:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://storkstudios.github.io/blog/demo_2_2_patchnotes/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Adam &amp;ldquo;Gahlammon&amp;rdquo; Dachtera, team leader and main designer of the Bullet Waste project, here to tell you about latest patches of our demo and to tease what will come next.&#xA;About the changes The patched version of our last demo was just released and I&amp;rsquo;d like to share with you a little bit about the things we&amp;rsquo;ve changed. The patches we included are mostly based on the issues that were problematic for the players and quick to fix for us.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learn about your own game using telemetry</title>
      <link>https://storkstudios.github.io/blog/learn_about_your_own_game_using_telemetry/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 23:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://storkstudios.github.io/blog/learn_about_your_own_game_using_telemetry/</guid>
      <description>Knowledge is power Video games are all about having fun. As a developer, you want your players to have a good time. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter whether it&amp;rsquo;s a crane operator simulator or a fast-paced shooter. You need to create an experience that people will like. The problem is, as the creator you are not a player, at least not a regular one. Your opinion on your game&amp;rsquo;s features and balance is heavily biased by your experience.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>So you want to have 5k active bullets at once...</title>
      <link>https://storkstudios.github.io/blog/so_you_want_to_have_5k_active_bullets_at_once/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 20:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://storkstudios.github.io/blog/so_you_want_to_have_5k_active_bullets_at_once/</guid>
      <description>Why As you may know Bullet Waste is a first-person bullet-hell game, which means spawning a lot of bullets at runtime. Furthermore, a game designer needs to be able to define complicated attacks with ease. This task was assigned to me and I think I&amp;rsquo;ve come up with a pretty interesting solution.&#xA;But how to tackle this This problem (as many others) consists of many smaller ones. But for the sake of this article lets focus on the main two:</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
